四个字的船 应该不是“船”
Joe,I don't think a four-letter word for "ship" can be "ship."
我以为那是免费赠品
I thought it was a freebie.
咦，这是什么？
Hello!What's this?
啊，对了，是那个女生的电话
Oh,right! It's that girl's phone number.
在这里，一个很辣的女生 给我的电话
There it is. Just a phone number...a really hot girl gave me.
也没什么，只是她家的电话…
It's no big deal. I mean,it is her home phone number,but....
真是的，差点就把这个宝贝掉了
Almost lost this baby!
可爱的亚曼达把电话给我 我却掉了
The lovely Amanda gives me her number,and I go and drop it.
谢谢
Thank you.
本集播出：“乔伊的新女友”
The One with Joey's New Girlfriend
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
瑞秋，你的生日是几号？
-When's your birthday?
5月5号，做什么？
-May 5th. Why?
我只是在记大家的生日
I'm making a list of birthdays.
我是12月… 随便
-Mine's December -Yeah,whatever.
她真漂亮
She's pretty!
好漂亮，真…好…真漂亮
Pretty,pretty girl. The pretty She's pretty.
去约她嘛
Go ask her out.
有什么大不了的？
-What's the worst that could happen?
我搞不好会死
-I could die.
一个人的确很难熬
Yeah,it's tough being single.
所以我很高兴我认识了亚曼达
That's why I'm so glad I found Amanda.
罗斯，你们只出去过一次
Ross,you guys went out once.
你们带着孩子去吃了一顿“小鸡奶酪”你都没亲她
You took your kids to Chuck E. Cheese,and you didn't even kiss her.
我会泄露秘密
I tell people secrets.
好让别人喜欢我
It makes them like me.
我只是想说 总算来了一段成熟的恋情
All I'm gonna say is,finally,it's nice to be in a mature relationship.
如果你真的只想说这句话 世界会更美好
You know,the world would be such a better place if that actually was all you were gonna say.
菲比，你生病了，别唱了 回家上床休息吧
Phoebe.You're sick. You shouldn't play. Go home.
但是我失业了
But I'm unemployed.
我只剩下音乐
My music is all I really have now.
音乐，还有自己做鞋子，很美吧？
Well,music and making my own shoes. Pretty,huh?
好，我去
All right,I'm gonna do it.
我去接受枪毙
I'm gonna go get shot down.
有什么建议？ 展现你的本色
Any advice?Just be yourself...
但是不要太过
...but not too much.
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
加油
Good luck!
请用祈祷的
Wish it!
你好，我坐在那里…
I was just sitting over there and....
我是钱德，我有说吗？
My name's Chandler. Did I say that?
没有，你好，我是凯西
No,you didn't. Hi,I'm Kathy.
K开头的还是C开头的凯西？-K开头的
-Kathy with a K or a C? -With a K.
你还真会搭讪
Wow,you are really good at this!
别这么说，我很尴尬
I'm out on a limb here!
你说得对，我道歉
I'm sorry. You're right.
但是我跟别人有约
But I should tell you,I'm waiting for a date.
他来了
And there he is now!
你们已经认识了
I see you guys already met.
是啊，我正在示范
I was trying to demonstrate...
如何把我那很大的脚
...how I could get my very large feet...
塞进我那更大的嘴里
...into my even bigger mouth.
我就说吧
Didn't I tell you?
他最爱现了
Always showing off.
首先我要说，我感冒了
Before I start,I want to say that I have a cold.
要是我唱到一半打喷嚏 那不是故意的
So if I sneeze during a song,it's not on purpose.
除了“胡椒人”的最后一句
Except the last verse of "Pepper People."
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们喂你吃什么？
What are they feeding you?
这声音不赖喔
This chick sounds good.
臭臭猫，臭臭…
Smelly cat
甘瑟，乖孩子，拿杯威士忌来
Gunther,be a good little boy and bring me a whiskey.
想不到半夜2点半 还要抢遥控器
At 2:30 a.m.,I didn't expect to have to fight over the remote.
对不起 我想看厄尼柯瓦克斯（喜剧演员）的节目
Sorry,there's this Ernie Kovacs thing I wanted to watch.
我也是要看那个
That's why I got up too.
不会吧？我爱死他了
You're kidding? I love him!
我爸以前都逼我熬夜陪他看
My dad made me stay up and watch reruns with him.
我爸也是 你爸也逼你看世界小姐选拔吗
Mine too. Did your dad also make you watch the Mr. Universe contest?
没有 我爸也没有
-No. -Well,me neither.
下午很抱歉 要是知道你们…我也不会…
I'm sorry about this afternoon. If I had known that you two,I never would have....
没什么
Oh,please.
乔伊说你们是在表演课认识的
Joey tells me you two met in acting class.
对，我们两个一组 乔伊选了三场戏
They teamed us up as partners. Joey picked three scenes for us to do.
三场都是亲热戏
All of them had us making out.
太好了，他原先都逼我跟他练
That's a good thing because he used to make me rehearse with him.
开始了吗？ 还没，但是这个伸缩扫把很棒
-ls it on? -No,but this Wonder Broom is amazing!
上帝啊！
Oh,my God!
开始了
It's on!
小不点，过来
Here we go,little fella.
那鸭子呢？
What about the duck?
鸭子会游泳 也对
The duck can swim.
烂泥巴鞋
My sticky shoes
沾满烂泥巴的鞋
My sticky,sticky shoes
你为什么黏着我不放，宝贝？
Why you stick on me?Baby
谢谢你的灯光亲爱的
Thanks for the lights,honey.
太精彩了
Way to go!
你的声音好有磁性
Your cold makes you sound great.
好好玩，我真是太性感了
It's fun. God,I love how sexy I am!
凯西，该走了 我们要去买仓鼠
Kath,we should get going. We're going to buy hamsters.
我喜欢仓鼠
I love them.
不是那样的 我在替一个医疗研究员工作
No,it's not like that. I work for a medical researcher.
去玩吧 好
-Well,have fun. -Okay.
医学界总算也在救助 生病的仓鼠了
It's nice that the medical community is trying to help sick hamsters
是啊 太好了
-lsn't it? -Yeah,it's great.
我喜欢凯西 对啊
You know what? I like Kathy.
我也是，她好酷好漂亮
Me too! She's so cool and pretty.
是啊，她…
She is.
她既聪明又风趣
She's smart and funny.
我们昨晚聊了一整夜 她聊到一些…
We were up all last night talking. She said the funniest thing about
怎样？
What?
你爱她
You love her.
我没有
No,I don't.
你有，钱德爱凯西
Yes,you do. Chandler loves Kathy.
菲比，饶了他吧 谢了，罗斯
-Come on,just lay off him. -Thank you.
他现在有点敏感 因为他恋爱了
He's a little sensitive right now because he's so in love!
好啦
All right.
凯西，我爱你
Kathy,I love you!
我得写一些悲情的歌 来配合我的新哭腔
I need to write some depressing stuff to go with my new bluesy voice.
但是我没有悲惨的遭遇
But nothing that sad has ever really happened to me.
你妈自杀的事呢？
How about your mom dying?
或是你14岁时流落街头？
Or having to live on the streets when you were 14?
我可以写头发翘起来那次
I could write about the time my hair did that whoo-hoo thing.
我晚上要去亚曼达家
I'm going over to Amanda's tonight.
瑞秋不在
Rachel's not here.
你跟她进展如何？
How's it going with her?
很棒，搞不好今晚就有机会
Great,actually. I'm thinking tonight may be the night.
两个孩子会一起玩 等他们睡了
The kids are gonna play together,and then when they're asleep...
亚曼达和我再开一瓶酒
...I'm thinking Amanda and I break open a bottle of wine...
我们自己来玩
...do a little playing ourselves.
嗨，这是贾许
Hi,guys! This is Josh.
贾许，她们是我的朋友
Josh,these are my friends.
那是罗斯
And that's Ross.
贾许 你好
Josh,hi.
老兄
Dudes.
你在大学校队打球？
You played in college?
现在还是，明年我想进大学代表队
I still do. Next year,I hope to make varsity.
罗斯，你高中不是踢过足球吗？
Didn't you play soccer in high school?
不对 你只是用“海军准将64型”游戏机帮他们排赛程表
No,wait. You just organized their game schedules on your Commodore 64.
不早了，我还有球赛 先闪了
It's getting late. I gotta get to the game,so I'm gonna...head.
我会想你的
I'll miss you.
爽！
Dope!
很可爱嘛 非常可爱
Wow! Cute one.
我知道，他很棒吧？
-Very cute. -I know. Isn't he great?
总算来了一段有趣的恋情
So nice to finally be in a fun relationship,you know?
他一点也不无聊
There's nothing boring about him.
我敢赌他一定没进过博物馆
I bet he's never set foot in a museum.
也许他快要有机会了
Maybe he'll get to go soon.
像班级旅行什么的
Like on a class trip or something.
你们知道他还有哪里好？
You know what else is great about him?
该怎么形容 房间里没有恐龙玩具的男人？
What is the word for an adult who doesn't have dinosaur toys in their bedroom?
什么意思？
What was that?
莫妮卡知道
Monica knows.
那是罗斯发明来唬爸妈的
It's this dumb thing that Ross made up to try to fool our parents.
其实就是竖中指的意思
It's a way of giving the finger without actually having to give it.
你发明这个手势让我哭了
I cried the night you made that up.
我第一次明白我比我哥酷
It was the first time I realized I was cooler than my big brother.
我要去准备…
I'm going to go get ready...
赴今晚的约了
...for my date tonight...
先闪了
...so I'll just "head."
我也该走了，1小时后要上台
I should go too. I'm playing in one hour.
你们应该来听
You guys should come hear me.
来听
Hear me.
烂泥巴鞋…
My sticky shoes
我的性感破锣嗓没了
I lost my sexy phlegm!
班
Hi,Ben.
你好美 谢谢
-You look great! -Thanks.
汤米
Hey,Tommy!
我好高兴你今晚能来
I am so glad that you could come over tonight.
不，这是我的荣幸
Oh,no. It's my pleasure.
我的手机号码在餐台上 冰箱里的东西自己拿
My cell phone number is here on the counter.Please,help yourself to anything in the fridge.
真的很谢谢你 我想约这个男的好久了
I appreciate this so much. I have been trying to go out with this guy for a month.
我…
I...
能不能请你等孩子睡了再喝酒
I'd really appreciate it if you'd wait and drink your wine after the kids are asleep.
成人频道锁码了 密码是43…
I blocked the adult channels for the other babysitters,but the code is four,three
不用了
I'm fine.
谢谢你，希望改天我也能帮你
Thanks for this. I hope I can do the same for you sometime.
谁想打长途电话？
Who wants to make some long-distance calls?
凯西，凯西，喂
Kathy! Kathy! Hi!
凯西，凯西
Kathy! Kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
去接，去接
Fetch! Fetch it!
凯西，凯西，凯西
Kathy! Kathy!Kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
钱德，你怎么在这里？
Chandler,what are you doing here?
我只是来打个招呼
I just wanted to say,"Hey!"
好
Hey.
你说得太严重了吧
You're making it sound worse than it was.
她的男伴给了我10块钱
Her date tipped me $10!
菲比，你干什么？
What are you doing?
我想恢复性感，所以我想感冒
I want to be sexy again,so I'm trying to catch a cold.
应该很容易，感冒很常见
Should be easy. They're pretty common.
你会得肺炎
You'll catch pneumonia!
你们说得对 我爱上了乔伊的女朋友
Okay,you were right. I'm in love with Joey's girlfriend.
什么？ 真的吗？
-What? -Are you serious?
怎么可能？你们根本不熟
How is that possible? You barely know her.
我不晓得，我就是…
I don't know. I just
我就是无法忘掉她
I can't get her out of my head.
我很糟糕，非常非常糟…
I'm a very bad person. I'm a very,very bad person.
我是个烂人
I'm a horrible person.
“才不是呢，钱德，我们还是爱你”
"No,you're not. We still love you,Chandler!"
我染上你的感冒了
Phoebe,I think I caught your cold.
是偷走才对
You mean you stole it!
打喷嚏不要捂嘴巴
Don't cover your mouth when you do that!
我们正在说你
We were just talking about you.
真的？
Really?
对，就是你喝醉 头泡在马桶里睡着那次
The time you got drunk and fell asleep with your head in the toilet.
就是在那里
Right in there!
你们租了什么电影？ 还是一样
-What movie did you get? -I got what I always get.
“虎胆龙威”
Die Hard.
我就是喜欢乔伊这一点
That's what I like about Joey. Any other guy would have been:
其他人都会说 “我也最喜欢‘英国病人’”
"Yeah,The English Patient is my favorite movie too."
但乔伊就会说 “才不要，借‘虎胆龙威’”
But Joey goes,"No way. Let's get Die Hard.
“我才不看那个英国病人”
I'm not watching that English crap."
是啊，他最棒了
Yeah,he's dreamy.
我先走了，我跟朋友有约
I gotta go. I gotta go meet some friends.
他有别的朋友？
He has other friends?
99…100
Ninety-nine...
我来捉你们了
...a hundred. Ready or not,here I come!
我再解释一次规则
Let's go over the concept one more time.
小家伙们
Hi guys
晚上要不要跟我们吃饭？
You want to get some dinner with me and Kathy tonight?
我已经吃饱了
You know what? I already ate.
才4点半
It's 4:30.
我星期一吃得很饱
I had a big meal on Monday.
可以撑一整个礼拜
So that'll get me straight through the week.
好，我知道是怎么回事
I see what's going on here.
你知道？
-You do? -Yeah.
对，你不喜欢凯西
You don't like Kathy.
被你猜对了
You got me.
我们交往至今，你一直在躲她
You've been avoiding her ever since we started going out.
我曾经努力去喜欢珍妮丝
I made an effort to like Janice.
现在该你试着去喜欢凯西 陪我们去吃饭了，对吧？
Now I think it's your turn to make an effort to like Kathy by going out with us. Right?
对，没错
-Yeah,right.
很好，而且我请客
-Good. And hey,my treat.
不过你不吃，对吧？ 对
-Only because you're not eating,right? -Right.
奶奶，对不起
Sorry,Grandma.
罗斯不在
Ross isn't here.
放手
Stop it!
那我们派对上见
I'll see you at the party?
啤酒免费，24小时乘以七天！
Beer's fear,man! Twenty-four,seven!
我一定会嫁给他
I am so gonna marry that guy.
怎么了？
What?
我觉得他偷我的钱
-I think he's stealing from me.
为什么？
-Why?
因为他真的偷我的钱
Because he's stealing from me!
是我，还有热汤
Hi,it's me and soup.
我刚遇到贾许，他穿你的皮衣看起来好帅
I just saw Josh. He looked so yummy in your leather jacket.
来，我不吃鸡，所以只有汤
I don't eat chicken,so it's just noodle soup.
熬汤时又没放鸡，跟水没两样
There's no chicken in the broth,so it's really just noodle water.
谢谢你
-Thank you so much. -Sure.
你拿那个干嘛？
What are you doing?
我要你的细菌，我想再感冒
I need your germs. I want my cold back.
我怀念我的性感嗓音
I miss my sexy voice.
对不起
Sorry,Phoebe.
没关系
It's okay.
汤好喝吗？
How's the soup?
那个女生的内衣都露出来了
Check it out! You can see that girl's underwear.
她很棒吧？
Is she great,or what?
你觉得她如何？
What do you think?
她不是我的型
She's not really my type.
不是你的型？大美女耶
Not your type? She's gorgeous.
因为她穿网袜
You know what it is? The fishnet stockings.
看到女生穿网袜，我就想到…
Whenever I see a girl in fishnet stockings,it reminds me of...
我爸穿网袜的样子
...my father in fishnet stockings.
好吧 我有点了解你为何单身了
Understanding a little more of why you're single.
我有个很漂亮的朋友 我们可以一起约会
I have a friend you'd like. She's really pretty. And then we could double date.
不必了
No,thanks.
好 我也有几个丑朋友没有对象
I've got some ugly friends,and they're all available too.
我去叫酒
I'm gonna grab a beer.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你什么意思？
-What was that? -What?
什么？ 凯西在示好，你却掉头就走
Kathy's being really nice and you just walked away.
我们不是说好了？
I thought we had a deal.
你要我怎样？
What do you want from me?
我要你喜欢她
I want you to like her.
要是太难了 你起码可以装一下
If that's too damn difficult for you,then the least you could do is pretend.
我正在装啊
-I am pretending.
那就再像一点
-Then do it better.
好，不如我去说我很喜欢她
What do you say I go over there and tell her how much I like her?
我可以说我一直在想她
I can tell her how much I've been thinking of her.
认识之后我就一直想着她
I haven't stopped thinking about her since we met.
我无可救药 简直想掐死自己的爱着她
I'm so over the top,want-to-slit-my-own-throat...
每一天的每一分每一秒
...in love with her that for every minute...
我都在怨恨为何是你先认识她
...I can't believe my own damn bad luck that you met her first!
很不错
That's pretty good.
但是别那么夸张
But you might want to tone it down a little.
我还在发烧？ 你确定温度计没坏？
I still have a fever? Are you sure that thing's working right?
我们可以量你的其他地方
Well,we could take it the other way.
是亚曼达载我来的
So Amanda just dropped me off.
我就喜欢她这一点
That's one of the things I love about her.
成年人可以开车
She's old enough to drive.
你晚上不去找爸妈了？
You're not going to Mom and Dad's tonight?
不了，对不起
No,sorry.
亚曼达呢？
Where's Amanda?
瑞秋，帮我拿咳嗽药水好吗
Could you get me some cough drops?
我在想 你可以带她去你的旧房间
I'm thinking you could bring her...and you guys could go up to your old room
然后不上床
... and not make out.
罗斯，咳嗽药水
Cough drop,please?
至少她跟我出去 不是为了看限制级电影
At least she's not going out with me to get into R-rated movies.
你怎么不娶她算了？
Why don't you just marry her?
我忘了，你不行 她不是同性恋
Wait,you can't! I forgot. She's not a lesbian.
亚曼达和我… 什么都不是
-Amanda and I have a -You have nothing!
你们根本没在约会 你是她的保姆
You're not even going out! You're her babysitter.
你在做12岁小女生做的事
You have a 12-year-old girl's job!
真可悲啊
That is so sad.
你笑什么 你男朋友还不是爱喝酒又偷钱
And what are you laughing at,Miss My-keg-sucking-boyfriend...-is-stealing-from-me?
他偷了几块钱又怎样 他有买东西给我
So he stole a couple bucks from me. Big deal!At least he got me something with it.
那是我的
That's mine!
你们两个成熟一点好吗？
Would you both please start acting like adults?
把咳嗽药水拿给我
And give me my cough drops!
好 对不起
-Fine. -Sorry.
拿去
Here.
至少我还赚了10块钱
At least I made $10 in my relationship.
你…
You know...?
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
在大街上游行
Parading down the street
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
留下小脚印
Leaving little treats
用这种声音唱还能听吗？
Does it even work without my sexy voice?
我喜欢
I like it.
甘瑟，亲我
-Gunther,kiss me. -What?
副警长，快想办法
Do it,deputy! Do something!
我们没有要睡，但是小声点好吗
We aren't exactly sleeping in here,but do you mind?
我可以睡你的沙发吗？
Can I sleep on your couch?
我还在等我的纸黏土人
And I'm still waiting For my papier-mache man
谢谢各位
Thank you,my babies.
瑞秋 怎样？
Rachel?
我不知道你有没有听说 我和菲比的事
Did you hear what happened between me and Phoebe?
没有
No
我们接吻了 不是我主动的，但我也没阻止
We kissed. I didn't initiate it,but I also didn't stop it.
我一直觉得很内疚
I've been feeling guilty.
好
Okay.
所以…我们没事吧？
So...are we cool?
好
Okay.
我就知道你会谅解
I knew you would understand.